A day like this does come
ويأتي يوم مثل هذا
I can't believe I'm coming back to Korea
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنني سأعود إلى كوريا
How do you feel?
كيف تشعر؟
President, the investment you proposed was Have you thought about it?
سيدي الرئيس، الاستثمار الذي اقترحته كان هل فكرت في ذلك؟
Take over this hotel Just a little bit of remodeling
تولي هذا الفندق فقط القليل من إعادة البناء
You will be very successful
سوف تكون ناجحا جدا
Then right away You become the owner of the hotel.
ثم على الفور تصبح مالك الفندق.
He is also the owner of a super luxury hotel.
وهو أيضًا صاحب فندق فاخر للغاية.
Well, I'm thinking about it.
حسنا، أنا أفكر في ذلك.
It is an unconditional business. Please review the business plan as well.
إنه عمل غير مشروط. يرجى مراجعة خطة العمل كذلك.
Boss Shin, come out, let’s do it together.
أيها الرئيس شين، اخرج، فلنفعل ذلك معًا.
Quickly
بسرعة
It's noisy
انها صاخبة
Oh my, fuck, I'm catching someone!
يا إلهي، اللعنة، أنا أقبض على شخص ما!
oh my god?
يا إلهي؟
Is this your family?
هل هذه عائلتك؟
Please catch that guy
يرجى القبض على هذا الرجل
How much did you decide to get?
كم قررت أن تحصل عليه؟
10 times
10 مرات
I'll give you 10 times more
سأعطيك 10 مرات أكثر
Don't be fooled! It's a lie!
لا تنخدع! إنها كذبة!
I'll give you more, that much
سأعطيك المزيد، هذا القدر
Catch those bastards
القبض على هؤلاء الأوغاد
Stop! Don't move!
توقف! لا تتحرك!
Stay still
ابق ساكنا
That guy is a criminal
هذا الرجل مجرم
we reported it
أبلغنا عنه
From vandalism to violence
من التخريب إلى العنف
Who's in charge here!
من المسؤول هنا!
Subtitle: Ahn Hyo-mi
العنوان الفرعي : آهن هيو مي